Theme Tune: [music playing]
Codey: Hello farmers and welcome to another episode of the harvest season. My name is Codey. And
Chelsea: And my name is Chelsea. Woo! Woo!
Codey: we are here today to talk about cottagecore games. Oh, woo. Oh, oh, oh. Specifically,
Codey: we have Chelsea on here as our neopets correspondent. So we're going to talk about neopets today.
Chelsea: I've studied my whole life for this moment.
Codey: Which is a little different than like normal cottagecore games, but it sure does have that
Codey: cottagecore feeling in our hearts, right? And so I think so. Yeah, somewhere in there.
Chelsea: I think so. Deep in our warm fuzzies.
Codey: I will also mention I am not firing on all cylinders today. I have I don't know what's
Codey: up, but I feel like I have vertigo a little bit. But sitting in front of a microphone
Codey: and not moving shouldn't be a problem, so we're gonna see how this goes.
Codey: Thanks!
Chelsea: I think you're doing great.
Codey: Okay, so we're gonna talk about neopets.
Codey: Before that, we have some game news, but before that we're gonna talk about what we have been
Codey: up to.
Codey: Chelsea, what have you been up to?
Chelsea: Kids are back to school, uh, Legend of Zelda Ocarina of Time is coming out, life complete.
Codey: Mm-hmm have you that not attained yet?
Chelsea: Um, step one, obtain a Switch 2.
Chelsea: Not yet.
Codey: Okay.
Chelsea: And then I was like, "Oh, maybe I'll look at the pre-orders."
Chelsea: They're gone.
Codey: Yep there and it's gone.
Chelsea: And they're gone.
Codey: Um yeah I need to also secure a switch to uh not necessarily a Zelda edition.
Codey: Oh it's just 500 bucks that's not that bad.
Codey: That's not that bad.
Chelsea: Cries in Canadian, I think ours without without a game. I think it's 679
Codey: Yeah this is without a game it's but it's still 500.
Codey: Which is like I don't know not that not that bad.
Codey: Uh it's so oh.
Chelsea: No, and I looked into maybe trading in one of our switches
Chelsea: because we have a few and it's like $80 a game stop.
Chelsea: I'm like, yeah, no, you're not helping the stereotypes.
Codey: Yeah maybe I should do that too because we have two switches right now and I don't.
Codey: So I feel like there's something weird about that.
Codey: Like, they won't let you play.
Codey: like certain game. I don't know. I guess I'm trying to think about, like, if I have any game saves
Codey: that are, like, precious and dear to me, and I really don't think that that's true.
Chelsea: Yeah, I have my Animal Crossing Island, so we would just use one of the other ones, I think, to trade in.
Codey: Yeah. Yeah, I don't. I'm not that worried about it. And Jeff is, uh, my husband has, we, so he,
Chelsea: Um, well, we shall see.
Codey: he got a Steam Deck, and that's pretty much all that I've been playing lately as well. He actually
Codey: no longer gets to play his steam deck because I have co-opted it as
Codey: my organizing game device.
Chelsea: Well, in your vows, what's his is yours.
Codey: That's true. We didn't have Vows, but yeah, he's aware. He understands.
Chelsea: He knows what's up.
Codey: A lot of the time we'll be playing, um, like he'll, we'll be on the couch at night and he'll
Codey: like pull out his laptop to play a game that he could play on his steam deck. And then I just try
Codey: and hand him a steam deck and he's like, no, no, I know how it is. Like keep, keep sorting.
Codey: Well, it's just funny because I like offer it to him and he's like, no, no, it's fine.
Chelsea: Leave me and my arcane library out of it.
Chelsea: how nice of you to join us for an evening of gaming on the steam deck
Codey: So exactly.
Chelsea: yeah what have you been up to
Codey: Um, so I am officially fully moved in to New Jersey. Um, and I have already, so I started
Codey: volunteering at the American Museum of Natural History.
Codey: totally cool. I was fully expecting them to have like dozens of volunteers behind the scenes that
Codey: of people like me who got a degree but moved to the area and don't really have anything particular
Codey: going on like all of the jobs that I have right now are these like little part-time gigs where
Codey: like people send me stuff to identify and I identify it for them and then send it back and
Codey: then other than that I'm working on like my own projects and stuff so I kind of have like I can
Codey: volunteer my life however I wanted to be right now and so it I was like oh I have I basically
Codey: have time to volunteer at the museum and I was like I wonder if they'll be able to take me in
Codey: and they they actually have none volunteers so yeah there's not as many people most of the
Chelsea: Cool.
Chelsea: None?
Codey: volunteers so I just did volunteer orientation yesterday and there are they said there are 1100
Codey: volunteers at AMNH, but the majority of them
Codey: are mostly front-facing, so it's like the people that are giving little tours or
Codey: working at the information desk. The majority of those people are actually volunteering.
Codey: And then there are some of us who are "behind the scenes," and so I don't really work with
Codey: any of the public at all. I'm going to be in the collections, and the people that I'm going to be
Codey: volunteering for.
Codey: say that they just they have like maybe two volunteers right now but they're not sure if
Codey: they're gonna be around really because they've had like commitment changes lately and stuff
Codey: and so they don't really have anything and the collections that i'm working with are take up like
Codey: more than half of all of the invertebrate collections and so it's like a good amount
Chelsea: Oh wow.
Codey: of but and like the big part is the lepidoptera so the butterflies and the moths and the butterfly
Codey: collection on its own takes up so much space.
Codey: to do. I'm going to start with the butterfly. I'm going to start with the butterfly. I'm
Chelsea: No.
Chelsea: Okay, then yes.
Codey: he donated a bunch of them to
Codey: the American Museum of Natural History. And so, and they have them there. And when the curator was
Codey: giving me a tour, he like pointed out that they now have like a front facing exhibit that you can
Codey: like, as you're going and looking at the collections core, there's like a couple boxes, like
Codey: drawers, insect drawers of butterflies. And he's like, these are an abacos butterflies. And I put
Codey: them here because we get media requests for these butterflies all the time. And so I was giving a
Codey: lot of tours to people back behind the scenes to look at these butterflies.
Codey: So now I can just be like, "Oh yeah, there they are."
Codey: You don't have to come behind the scenes, you can just look at them right there.
Chelsea: Just open the drawer.
Codey: We'll not even open the door, it's part of the exhibits now.
Codey: So it's really cool and that's been really fun to start becoming integrated in there.
Codey: So I've done three days so far and I now have my badge so I now can get in and get around
Codey: for free.
Codey: You don't have to have someone come and babysit me.
Codey: And then yeah, and then I'm going to be getting an email, an AMNH email soon, which is pretty
Chelsea: Oh good, you get your behind the scenes access.
Codey: cool.
Codey: So and then on top of all that, I've been doing organizing games.
Codey: I would say the first organizing game I'm playing is apartment organization, which is
Codey: not as fun as the others, but I finished Big Bad Pharma, which is the pharmacy game.
Codey: Fixed the kerfuffle that we were having where for some reason, like American Express and
Codey: Steam were like fighting over the seven dollars or whatever it was that this game cost.
Chelsea: Yeah, yeah, I remember that.
Codey: And so but they've they figured it out.
Codey: So we're fine. So I'm playing it again.
Codey: Well, I finished it. And so I 100 percent of that.
Codey: And then I just picked up Sort Them Ducks and this is a ducks, a rubber ducky game.
Chelsea: Oh my gosh. Elaborate. Oh my gosh.
Codey: And so it's just like a space that has shelves and there's like categories.
Codey: There's like Beach is a category.
Codey: There's Mafia category and that category has an Al Capone duck and an Al Capone's wife
Codey: and a goon and a detective and an accountant.
Chelsea: Oh my god, I'm looking at this right now.
Codey: It's such a silly little game.
Chelsea: $7.97, yep.
Codey: Yeah, these games cost like nothing.
Chelsea: That's gonna go on.
Codey: It's nuts, but it's.
Chelsea: Developer Mr. Duck.
Codey: It's really fun, and the, um...
Codey: Some of the other, like, uh, ducks that you can find, like, as you're going through, you can, they have, like, the people that backed the game, like, the highest backers or whatever, they have ducks of their own, and so as you're sorting, you might come upon, like, an @whatever duck, like, whatever the content creator is, and then there's, in a special room, there's, like, a place to put those ducks.
Chelsea: Oh, this is such a good backer idea.
Codey: Yeah, it's really cute. I just realized
Codey: I found the mr. Duck one and I had no idea what to do with it
Codey: And now I realize because there's like five or six
Codey: Spaces that you can put like the content creator ducks like the backer ducks
Codey: But then there's one space across the room that I was like, I don't know what this is for
Codey: And then I realized I found mr. Duck the other day. I was like, I don't know where you go
Codey: I'm just gonna throw you back in the pile. And now I'm like, oh heck wait, that's he's probably the special
Chelsea: That's THE duck, that's Sir Duck.
Codey: Now that you said the developer
Codey: No
Chelsea: Now I gotta go find him back in the pile.
Chelsea: Wow, what did my voice just do there?
Chelsea: Now I gotta go find them back in the pile.
Codey: Yeah, one of my many piles so
Chelsea: Ah, that looks fun.
Chelsea: Yeah, I might be doing that.
Codey: It's a it's a cute little game it's definitely worth it so
Chelsea: No rush, no pressure, just ducks, is what it says.
Codey: Just ducks. Yep, and sometimes when you I don't know if it's every time when you pick them up or if it's only sometimes but
Codey: Like I'll pick them up and they make like a little quack noise
Codey: I don't know if it's just that I have my
Codey: switch or the steam
Codey: volume really low
Codey: And that's why I only hear it sometimes or what I don't know it's cute though
Codey: Yeah, so that is what we have been up to oh
Codey: Okay, so jumping into news now first up we have little witch in the woods
Codey: Has a release date trailer and a new release date. So it is coming to switch on
Codey: September 16th.
Codey: And the release date trailer is pretty cute, kind of shows some of the mechanics in the game that are kind of unique, I think, that looked pretty nice.
Codey: At one point in the trailer, there was a cat that you threw a fish at or something. I'm not entirely sure what happened, but it then flops onto its side.
Codey: It looked really cute. You zoom around on a broom, so it looks like they're a sprint mechanic or whatever.
Codey: just you on a broom. dash. um and then it also looks like there's a research mechanic so there's
Chelsea: - Oh my God.
Chelsea: - Dash on your broom.
Codey: a there was a um like creature that was walking around and then you kind of like your character
Codey: is like scribbling a notebook and then it opens up the encyclopedia and like that page is now
Codey: generated and it has like information about that so I don't know if there's like if that's kind of
Codey: like a research mechanic kind of like research story or if it's just i'm not I don't know
Codey: I don't know but it looked cool I was like oh that's cool like it is kind of a world
Codey: that you can explore and and better understand um yeah it looks cute oh dang okay cool yeah that's
Chelsea: - Yeah, it looks super cute.
Chelsea: That comes out next week too, September 16th.
Codey: wow we're flying through september y'all
Codey: oh my gosh um next up is Pokopia so we have more deal more details on the dlc
Codey: Um, the 2nd, part of the DLC that is coming.
Codey: So, uh, in this DLC, there are many different accessories, so it kind of showed off a lot of the different accessories.
Codey: Including, uh...
Chelsea: Dodo duo wheeling some sunglasses.
Codey: [laughs]
Codey: Yeah, including some sunglasses, which is really cute.
Codey: Of course, they had a squirrel showing off the sunglasses.
Codey: There's a couple different types of bows, um, very cute.
Codey: And they also added new Pokémon, so they added Skitty, Doduo, and Snubbull.
Codey: I'm very excited. I still don't have this game.
Codey: I'm still not going to get this game, but I was very happy to see Skitty.
Codey: I love Skitty.
Codey: It's just such a cute little g..., cute little Pokémon.
Codey: And I don't know, Chelsea, do you know what is special about Skitty in the Pokédex in Pokémon Go?
Codey: It is the only Pokémon facing left.
Chelsea: what is it oh my oh I did not know that
Codey: So every other Pokémon, to my knowledge, in the Pokémon Go Pokédex is facing to the right or something like that.
Chelsea: uh
Codey: It's just like, screw you, I do what I want.
Codey: It's facing the opposite direction.
Chelsea: a fellow lefty icon I love it
Codey: Oh my gosh, speaking of lefty icon, did you see the new iPhone that's releasing or whatever?
Codey: Okay, so they're releasing a new iPhone and that phone now has a touch instead of having a face ID because that doesn't work with how it's shaped.
Chelsea: No, why would
Codey: They now are going to have a touch, like a thumbprint marker or whatever.
Codey: And you just do that by touching the power button, which is on the right side of the phone.
Codey: Which is like left-handed people get screwed.
Chelsea: No, it's not.
Codey: You're not going to be able to just automatically open.
Chelsea: Yeah, I'm left-handed.
Codey: And it pitches it.
Codey: All you have to do is just put your finger over here and it just unlocks immediately.
Codey: And you're like, oh no!
Chelsea: I'm not holding it that way.
Codey: That's not, left-handed people are not, their thumb is not over there, my guy.
Chelsea: Oh, they don't have like an accessibility. They'll release the exclusive left handed mode later.
Codey: Or just a flop, like, I can't, that'd be so funny if there's just a swapped iPhone.
Codey: There's just a left-handed iPhone that has the power button on the other side, I doubt it.
Chelsea: Well, I remember on the Google Pixel, you could do the thumbprint on the back, I think.
Codey: Okay.
Chelsea: And I was able to use my left hand, I think.
Chelsea: I'm pretty sure.
Chelsea: This was a few years ago.
Chelsea: But I have an Apple now, but I don't know.
Chelsea: I don't know about how I feel about that.
Codey: - Well, it's also like a folding phone, so who knows?
Chelsea: Oh, it's that one.
Codey: I, I'm a little sus.
Codey: Yeah, I'm a little sus about the folding phones myself.
Codey: If I'm gonna, if I want a phone that folds,
Chelsea: Yeah, I was literally about to say Razor and Shambles, no, I want a Razor.
Codey: I'm gonna get a Razr.
Codey: Come on now.
Chelsea: And then a few years ago when the Barbie movie released, they had the Nokia Barbie phone.
Chelsea: It was a pink flip phone, and when you open it, it goes, "Hi, Barbie!"
Codey: yeah oh my gosh
Chelsea: And then the first contact in there is Ken.
Chelsea: And I want it so bad because I am so sick of, like, I'm just going to brick my phone, make it boring.
Codey: yeah this is the the year of people going analog is what they call it
Chelsea: Yes! Do you remember Hit Clips?
Codey: yeah like the little like a song in a 30 second clip
Chelsea: You would get, like, a 30-second clip. It would just repeat ad nauseum.
Codey: Yeah, it was like a it was like a Game Boy.
Chelsea: And we were thankful for the opportunity.
Codey: that just had 30 seconds of a of a song
Chelsea: Yes!
Codey: you could put into the little thing. Oh, my goodness.
Codey: Y'all, this is a nostalgia episode. Just a heads up.
Chelsea: It is. Heads up, 90s kids unite.
Codey: We're coming.
Codey: Next up is Disney Dreamlight Valley.
Codey: So they have a new DLC coming out called the Keepsake Sea.
Codey: It adds underwater.
Codey: And Al said, huh?
Codey: A cozy game with farming getting an underwater DLC in 2026.
Codey: how original.
Codey: um Al being spicy he has some he has some awesome comments on some of these things so uh and in
Codey: the underwater you'll see it adds mermaid tails which I kind of like so when i've been playing
Codey: this game so far like ariel is just in the water and there is a water source in like all of the
Codey: different zones but it just feels like ariel's just kind of like left out because she doesn't
Codey: get to like there's like the shop or whatever though I think they did add it so that she has
Codey: has like leg, they gave her.
Codey: Legs at one point, but at the beginning it's like she was just yeah, she was just stuck
Chelsea: Just, just watching from the ocean.
Codey: in any like water source.
Codey: So I kind of like the idea of adding an underwater component and like you get a tail like I think
Codey: Ursula like curses you or something like gives you the ability to have a tail and it shows
Codey: that you can add like a new underwater so you can basically like put houses underwater
Codey: now for like the people that have underwater houses, which was really cool.
Codey: They've also added some new characters.
Codey: So they're adding Meg from Hercules, Captain Jack Sparrow from Pirates of the Caribbean
Codey: and Al wrote the guy from Atlantis and he said he didn't remember his name and his name
Codey: is Milo.
Codey: Al, come on now.
Chelsea: I love how we both jumped on it. Milo!
Codey: Milo Thatch.
Chelsea: Yeah, come on. Get with it.
Codey: Yeah, so when they show Captain Jack Sparrow and like all the characters at one point you're
Chelsea: Please read this comment that's underneath there.
Codey: like running down the dock he's running
Codey: like an idiot and like I get that in the in those games like sorry in the
Codey: movies Captain Jack Sparrow does he never runs normal so like I get it but
Codey: the way it's just the way he runs is just so it's goofy on another level so
Chelsea: He's got those heavy boots on!
Codey: he those boots are not that I don't know so there is that and that is coming out
Codey: I don't, I don't know if it has...
Codey: a date I think it just said like soon or whatever and then next up is outbound
Codey: they have a wildlife...
Chelsea: Oh sorry, it says, "Tune in to our showcase stream on October 21st."
Chelsea: So, hopefully around then.
Codey: Yeah, so maybe we'll get a release date on October 21st for that next up is outbound
Codey: They have a new update the wildlife update coming in fall in air quotes
Codey: They have a little teaser video. The teaser video itself is just showing the mechanic of taking photos of the camera
Codey: and
Codey: They say quote a lively world full of wild animals birds and insects
Codey: So I'm super excited to take photos of insects you guys I want to see some really cute
Codey: of insects like
Codey: Pollinating or eating things or I don't know just cute cute stuff. I want to see it
Codey: And the camera has a lot of customization options. So it showed that was what the teaser video shows
Codey: and basically there's
Codey: You can like change the saturation and the brightness and the contrast you can also change the depth of field, which I really liked
Codey: Because that is something that like is not really like you can choose what
Codey: It that's in your frame
Codey: And they show it happening with like I think it's an elk
Codey: Of like you focusing on the elk and it was really cool
Codey: And Al's comment is I moaned about fishing because as a concept it felt like it didn't fit well in this game
Codey: But photos of wildlife perfect more like this
Codey: correct
Chelsea: He's not- he's not a fishing fan, eh, in these games.
Codey: Well, it's just it's it's a little weird to add
Codey: fishing in outbound because you are at sea.
Codey: You're mostly just like exploring really and fishing didn't seem to fit that as well.
Chelsea: Yeah, maybe diving would have made more sense.
Codey: Yeah yeah but anyway the next big update after this is the big NPC update and that is basically
Codey: because most of the NPCs currently in the game are like on vacation or something. If you go
Codey: into their houses or come upon their houses they...
Codey: there are notes on it that are like come on in use whatever you need we're not
Codey: here and we won't be here and like one of them is like please water the cactus
Codey: or something like that so that'll be interesting to finally have NPCs in the
Codey: game and like other people to interact with next up is the farmer was replaced
Codey: so they have a new DLC I don't know if it's a DLC or just an update but it is
Codey: called "The Miner" was replaced.
Chelsea: - Uh-huh.
Codey: And this is releasing on November 2nd, and it adds that third dimension so it's instead of
Codey: Going across like a 2d space like you are actually going deep
Codey: The con or like lower down and the comment or the quote is "the DLC adds a brand new section to the unlocked tree with
Codey: plenty of new things to discover
Codey: Mine resources like coal and quartz sort mushrooms grow rice on clay and solve a minesweeper
Codey: inspired challenge, and much more.
Codey: And I got really excited about the Minesweeper thing.
Codey: Um, like once you hit a certain level depth, um, there's a
Codey: Minesweeper challenge at the bottom.
Codey: And I, I actually just got a new phone game.
Codey: That's like infinite Minesweeper or something like that.
Chelsea: Amazing.
Codey: Um, because I just loved this game so much as a kid.
Codey: And so, uh, 10 out of 10, I'm excited to try and figure out
Codey: how to code that.
Codey: Um, I might just honestly have to pass the, my, cause I can
Codey: play this on my computer.
Codey: I might just have to pass my computer to my husband and be
Chelsea: Um, can you do this for me?
Codey: like, figure out how to code this place.
Codey: Can you do this?
Codey: I just want to watch it happen, but I can't, I don't want to
Chelsea: That's super cool.
Codey: have to figure out how.
Codey: So yeah, this is something that's really cute.
Codey: Uh, releasing November 2nd and it's something Al and I will
Codey: definitely cover.
Codey: Next up we have Lou's
Codey: Lagoon. They have their 1.1.0 release. So they have fixed some things. They have sped
Codey: up crafting because it seemed really slow. There's more storage on your plane. And they
Codey: fixed a lot of bugs. There are many bug fixes in this list of things that they did. And
Codey: I just loved, I always, whenever I see a list of bug fixes or a list of like improvements
Codey: that were made, I love finding like.
Codey: looking through them like they're little easter eggs to try and find fun quotes and I found this
Codey: one "improved the tornado animation for more drama" and I said it's very important
Chelsea: [laughs]
Chelsea: They have their priorities in order.
Codey: yeah because I guess you get like shipwrecked at some point and there's a tornado and
Chelsea: [laughs]
Chelsea: It was not dramatic enough.
Codey: it wasn't dramatic enough and now it's very dramatic so
Chelsea: I love when developers put their little patch notes, like you said, the little tidbits, and then for Moonlight Peaks they did one and they're like, "We're sorry about the wine!"
Codey: you
Codey: [laughs]
Codey: Yeah.
Chelsea: Because they nerfed it so you couldn't sell it for as much money, and that was the big money maker in the game, so they're like, "We heard you about the wine, we're fixing it!"
Codey: Oh, no!
Codey: Oh.
Codey: Oh, yeah, I think I remember that.
Codey: Like, we talked about how they-
Codey: They, like, nerfed it and everyone was, like, so mad.
Codey: And...
Chelsea: Yeah, no, because that was our main money maker from the start.
Codey: Oh, that's so funny.
Chelsea: Yeah.
Codey: I was- So, I was thinking about that game.
Codey: Like, and that- That thing.
Codey: They have, wine and like, beer and stuff like that.
Codey: And I was trying to find, like, the game rating.
Codey: Because I remember when Apico was being made, they had, like, Mead.
Codey: Because you can make Mead with honey.
Codey: And Apico is, like, a beekeeping game.
Codey: And El, the developer, was talking about how they, like,
Codey: were trying to hit them with, like, an R rating.
Codey: Like, a- Or, sorry, rated M for Mature.
Codey: Because it was Mead.
Chelsea: Oh, so any alcohol needs to be...
Codey: And so, I was wondering if Moonlight Peaks probably also is rated M for Mature.
Codey: But it might also be rated that for other reasons.
Codey: Like, I don't know what the rest of the gameplay is.
Chelsea: here it's rated t yeah but it's crazy because like you have an openly alcoholic main character
Codey: What?
Codey: Dude.
Chelsea: that's always at the bar getting drunk and you have to like drag him back to his house and
Chelsea: he it's a huge plot line so i'm not sure yeah that's crazy about Apico
Codey: so funny yeah wild I wonder if it would be rated
Codey: different because he wanted it to be e for everyone
Codey: um because it's just a cute little beekeeping game but
Codey: whatever so they changed it to like apicola or something
Chelsea: [laughs] I love that.
Codey: it's whatever it works
Chelsea: [laughs] Ape-a-Cola.
Codey: uh and then finally we have palia uh quote this holiday season we're
Codey: we're launching a brand new feature called Echo Expedition.
Codey: Echo Expeditions bring you our own brand of wholesome dungeon crawling
Codey: while opening up new ways to progress, adventure, and team up with friends.
Codey: The feature brings replayable expeditions where pallians can delve through multitudes of levels,
Codey: tackle fantastical challenges, cleanse mysterious echo manifestations,
Codey: and grow stronger along the way.
Codey: And in the post about it, they made it clear that this does not have a lot of combat,
Codey: and so it's pretty light in combat, and it's PvP only, or sorry, PvE only,
Codey: so you're not going to be taking damage from your friends.
Codey: Yeah, so it just seems like it's a World of Warcraft dungeon-like thing,
Codey: where it's these replayable expeditions that you can do.
Chelsea: - Guess what, Al? (laughs)
Chelsea: Guess what, Al, guess what you're playing?
Codey: [laughs]
Codey: Yup.
Codey: Oh, I need to jump back into this.
Codey: I played this game a little bit when it first came out, I don't, actually I don't even think it was a 1.0 yet, um, but yeah, it is coming now out in "the holiday season".
Theme Tune: [upbeat music]
Kevin: Hi everyone, Harvest Season 1st, as you will notice, I am neither Cody nor Chelsea.
Kevin: Unfortunately, the recording, the episode they're working on for the first time ever
Kevin: had a bit of a major disruption, and they could not finish the recording.
Kevin: Everyone is now fine, thankfully, nothing too major, but yeah, they could not finish it.
Kevin: And so--
Kevin: We had to play by ear a little.
Kevin: Funnily enough, Chelsea and I were
Kevin: going to finish the episode on the topic that
Kevin: was originally planned.
Kevin: But some kerfuffles happened on our end as well.
Kevin: And here we are.
Kevin: Had too much to out-chagrin.
Kevin: We had to break out old reliable.
Kevin: And the rest of the episode will now
Kevin: be a Kevin Solo experience.
Kevin: Woo!
Kevin: [laughs]
Kevin: We'll also cover the other stuff,
Kevin: the Neopets stuff at a later time.
Kevin: But for now, let's see what I've got.
Kevin: And actually, that's a question I've been fumbling over
Kevin: for a little bit.
Kevin: Again, this is sort of last minute situation.
Kevin: I had a few ideas floating around,
Kevin: but they required a little more prep time.
Kevin: So I have opted for something I forgot
Kevin: I had in my back pocket.
Kevin: A... fourth?
Kevin: Third? I can't remember what number we were on.
Kevin: Well, the final discounting episode.
Kevin: Here we are! Surprise!
Kevin: Um...
Kevin: Because, uh, yeah.
Kevin: I... last time we talked about it
Kevin: with Al, I remember the big, was it
Kevin: People or Profit update?
Kevin: Um, which was good.
Kevin: I did not hit credits of that update
Kevin: at the time, and I since have.
Kevin: Uh, and I have
Kevin: more thoughts, um,
Kevin: on the endings and the overall experience.
Kevin: the end.
Kevin: This one is going to be a little more story heavy and character heavy because I think
Kevin: that's where a lot of the effort and energy was put in the update.
Kevin: I talked a lot about the mechanics last time and actually you know what let me follow up
Kevin: on that a little because yeah kind of revising my own notes from last time but one of my
Kevin: big complaints from the recording last time was...
Kevin: getting the new resources in the update for Discounty where they had introduced a number
Kevin: of new resources for all these new expansions and upgrades and such and I was having a lot
Kevin: of difficulty acquiring some.
Kevin: So as it turns out the real issue was less about the generation of the resources and
Kevin: more about, uh, I don't know, guiding the plow.
Kevin: Um, uh, because yeah, uh, essentially a bunch of new projects open up all over town when you reheat very early in the, uh, discounted post game update and, um, you're given story wise, uh, directed into a few of them, but not a lot of them.
Kevin: Um, and that's unfortunate because, uh, a lot of them are really useful and would be make more sense to unlock.
Kevin: Uh, if anyone's playing discounting out there, um, unlock the mine when you do the people are profit update, um, because that's how you get your metal and that you need metal for a lot of other things.
Kevin: Um, also a lot of story triggers are hidden behind, um, uh, the lab, uh, the, you unlock this lab as you go through the game.
Kevin: Um, and it's, it's a lot of story triggers and upgrades like the self checkout is hidden behind the lab. Um, but again, not super.
Kevin: Heavily indicated that's the way to go to do all of that, which is, uh, unfortunate.
Kevin: Um, that's the only real, um, like big criticism I have of the discounting update.
Kevin: Uh, at, at this point, like if they could have just sequenced that or pushed you a little harder, uh, to this correct ones in, in a optimal order, I think the experience would be a lot better.
Kevin: Um, but hey, you know, I guess that's maybe what the Internet for is
Kevin: for, but this county is kind of still a bit of a small game. I haven't found much in terms of
Kevin: online guides and advice, even now. But, but yeah, saying again, mechanically, a lot of upgrades are
Kevin: there. Some of the best customizations, some of the best mechanical upgrades for your store,
Kevin: including, again, the self-checkout, the online order area.
Kevin: On some of the best shelves and displays.
Kevin: stands and such, um, yeah, a bit unfortunate that they, um, didn't quite guide you to that,
Kevin: um, a little more clearly. Um, but anyways, I digress. Yeah. Gameplay wise, that's the only,
Kevin: uh, thing I think I really have to add. Uh, again, I think I've covered it pretty thoroughly
Kevin: in the other episodes. Um, uh, I guess, oh, the self-checkout since Al, I think would be curious
Kevin: about the automation. The self-checkout is not that big of an automation.
Kevin: So, you know, the number of customers you have in your store vary depending on your
Kevin: advertisements and whatnot. But I'd say maybe at most 10% of the customers will actually
Kevin: go through the self-checkout. And it actually still does require some player input because
Kevin: it'll have a malfunction or an error and you need to go just basically push a button on
Kevin: machine to keep, so the customer can keep
Kevin: on the machine. So, unfortunately, now it doesn't quite annihilate the checkout gameplay.
Kevin: But I mean, I was fine with that because I thought the gameplay was fine.
Kevin: Okay, I'm trying to think. Yeah, nothing too big. I need to go into detail. Because there's a lot of
Kevin: other nice little quality of life upgrades through those various lab projects like I talked about.
Kevin: But but yeah
Kevin: Nothing like worth diving into too far
Kevin: Anyways, okay, but all that said let's talk about the story
Kevin: Because that
Kevin: Is I think kind of the the the big thing that I haven't delved too deep into and now I have all the pieces
Kevin: more or less
Kevin: I think
Kevin: Well, I say more or less because we have the asterisk
Kevin: There are actually three endings with the people or profit update the good ending the bad ending and the mixed ending
Kevin: I you know in my defense
Kevin: I have only done the good ending but I have done a little research into the other endings to get an idea of what was
Kevin: Going on. Oh one nice little mechanical thing
Kevin: Basically the developers once you clear the game the the update ending they will
Kevin: They allow you to say, "Here's an extra save file if you want."
Kevin: It starts right at the beginning of the Paper Profit Update, so you can just go right into one of the other endings if you want to.
Kevin: Which is a really nice touch. They set that up right there for you.
Kevin: I haven't taken advantage of it, but it is there.
Kevin: And you know, once you do figure out the right upgrade path and whatnot, I do think the update is pretty quick to knock out.
Kevin: Not terribly huge of a chore, I think, to go back and do those other endings if you'd like.
Kevin: Okay, but before I talk about these endings, I actually do think I have to go a little bit into detail on some of these characters and their story arc.
Kevin: Because the endings, I think, are a little more tied to their individual arcs and progressions.
Kevin: Which is nice, because again, going back to one of the earlier episodes, that was one of the big things they were lacking in the ending.
Kevin: There was some closure in some of those character developments.
Kevin: uh... but uh... I think they have come
Kevin: full circle as interesting actually
Kevin: uh...
Kevin: how they approach some of these uh... but i'll get to that okay
Kevin: uh... but yeah let let me do a quick
Kevin: uh... just intro on some of the
Kevin: key characters
Kevin: uh...
Kevin: uh... so what the first one first character that you really mean the games
Kevin: name and teller
Kevin: as she's your aunt and in the base game the actual owner of discounting on she
Kevin: has your managing and running it but she is the actual owner and
Kevin: uh... makes the executive decisions uh...
Kevin: during the base game and teller is big on expanding discounting
Kevin: uh... and that uh... is what leads to a lot of conflict with a lot of other
Kevin: characters uh... including
Kevin: uh... what was her name I believe it's grace an employee who
Kevin: is your mentor but then gets fired to cut costs uh...
Kevin: uh... and also leads into conflict at the rest of the town as teller tries to
Kevin: explain too much and
Kevin: uh... basically
Kevin: demolish a historical
Kevin: quote landmark of the town excuse me in the people are profit update um she takes a much
Kevin: more backseat sort of role she's done some reflecting and has decided that she doesn't
Kevin: want to live the you know sort of high profit corporate grinding lifestyle and she decides
Kevin: leaves discounting more or less in your care um uh for you to decide how to go about it now
Kevin: Um, actually this is
Kevin: little, I guess, quirk of their update.
Kevin: The update, or the storyline through the update, makes sense if there's
Kevin: a period of time in between the base game and
Kevin: the update. Which, you know, for the player, I'm sure that's exactly what it was a number of months later,
Kevin: the progression of characters, the reflecting and changing
Kevin: their attitudes. That makes sense. But in game, there's no...
Kevin: no real indication of that. There might be a brief text thing that I don't remember, but
Kevin: I imagine for someone who goes through the whole game right now, start to finish,
Kevin: including the post-game stuff, we'll find it kind of jarring, almost comical,
Kevin: how some of these characters will shift their position or how they'll change their interaction
Kevin: with you. Anyways, so yeah, again, Head Teller, she's a big driving force of the base game,
Kevin: but much more laid off in the
Kevin: uh post game um the other key characters let's talk about um sammy the uh major
Kevin: power business woman she runs the actual like industrial factory plastic plant in town um and
Kevin: she is aggressive um she is uh yeah very profit motivated and only cares about business and the
Kevin: um and she personality wise she's abrasive and uh does not care much about anyone else other than
Kevin: herself um which uh yeah leads to a lot of conflict with a lot of the other small business owners
Kevin: even her own husband derek who is a bank manager in town um has uh issues that he's trying to
Kevin: resolve with her um which actually becomes a bit of a plot point in the
Kevin: post game but I will get to that um there are the uh three business owners uh the small business
Kevin: owners uh excuse me um there is parl uh the farmer there is fisher I believe the fisherman
Kevin: and barbara the fish plant owner apologies if I missed up their names it's been a while and i'm
Kevin: I'm going off my memory here, but there are three--
Kevin: small-ish business owners in town. They provide a lot of inventory for your store.
Kevin: And to kind of recap the base game, there's a few different plot lines. As I talked about, the
Kevin: town is kind of struggling with its identity, whether to grow, keep growing, or maintain its
Kevin: small-town feel and kind of history of sorts even though it's
Kevin: origin small-town with not much to claim but there are people in town who care
Kevin: about it like these small business owners but there's on this comes in
Kevin: conflict again with the expansion of businesses and and and whatnot this
Kevin: manifests itself through environmental issues there's a number of them crop up
Kevin: throughout the throughout the base game and mystery behind that is
Kevin: of a key aspect of the base game story and how the story ends there is a report
Kevin: that is basically confirms that it is not Tammy's fault which everyone had
Kevin: expected but it is actually the fault of the three business owners who had been
Kevin: using some bad business practices and we're polluting the ocean the air and so
Kevin: on um excuse me
Kevin: yeah the that actually that report is kind of a climax towards the base game
Kevin: and is one of the quote-unquote key decision points whether you try to side
Kevin: with the business owners and hide or obfuscate the results of the report or
Kevin: you try to just let it out honestly and paint Tammy in a better light despite
Kevin: her personality and practices um anyway so that's kind of I think roughly the
Kevin: setup for the the the base game and so that leads us to the people or profit
Kevin: update after we view the again kind of climax with the town meeting resulting
Kevin: in the revelation one way or the other no matter what your choice the truth
Kevin: does come out thanks aunt teller the the revelation of why there's been
Kevin: issues. At first, the three small business people will not shop at your store and you
Kevin: damage their relationship, but in People or Profit, they have decided to change their minds
Kevin: and they have formed a basically a cooperative, a small business sort of union sort of
Kevin: endeavor to try to be more sustainable and ecologically friendly after the
Kevin: debacle of the report and the issues the town is facing. And so the post-game story kind
Kevin: of starts with that. They contact you and they want to invite you into this union
Kevin: and they ask for your support and the very first task is to create a billboard
Kevin: and the billboard to advertise the new found business union. However, Tammy approaches you
Kevin: being a little more favorable with you since her name was more or less cleared from the
Kevin: original town report. She offers to help you grow your business,
Kevin: but it makes it very clear that will likely come at the cost of or at the detriment of the town
Kevin: or the other small businesses as she views their sustainability practices and whatnot as a threat
Kevin: to her.
Kevin: And so here's really the big first choice point. Do you make the ad to support Tammy and your own discounting store or do you promote the new business union?
Kevin: And this is basically how the update plays out. It's very clear, like A or B sort of choices, Tammy's side or the business union side.
Kevin: And so as you make more of the, basically the ending is determined by the number of choices you make in either side, right?
Kevin: If you basically pick all the union side, you'll get the good ending. If you pick all the Tammy side, you get the bad ending.
Kevin: There is actually a good ending, the neutral quote unquote mixed ending, which involves getting a bit of balance of both options of good and bad.
Kevin: Um, okay, so, uh, with...
Kevin: That kind of groundwork, um, the town does grow a little as the union tries to involve some more, uh, small business people into town.
Kevin: Um, they're quite an amusing crew, actually.
Kevin: Um, apologies, I do not have their names off the top of my head again.
Kevin: Um, but, uh, there is...
Kevin: Okay, here we go. I got okay. Apologies. Um, well anyways, uh, so the business union invites three
Kevin: uh new small local business people, um, there is
Kevin: Angeal who opens up a sort of health organic shop
Kevin: um, which is very funny, um because a lot of the
Kevin: small town, uh people
Kevin: Very, uh reluctant to try her wares
Kevin: um, and that's where you come in to play her because you can uh,
Kevin: provide some of her wares.
Kevin: through this county and then that helps her out there is a C actually a teenager
Kevin: who is a friend of one of the other residents in town she's a bit of a
Kevin: rebellious teenager and her store is in part determined by what your choices if
Kevin: you side of the Union you kind of force Casey to go on the straight and narrow
Kevin: and she starts up a lemonade stand and selling cookies.
Kevin: out of her car.
Kevin: It's very funny because it's tricked out and playing a bunch of music.
Kevin: But she if you side
Kevin: with the bad side, she can be selling some black market goods,
Kevin: which is pretty funny, too.
Kevin: And then the last character is
Kevin: best part, who is actually Tammy's brother.
Kevin: He's moved to town at the behest of Tammy.
Kevin: Also, who is trying to get her to produce
Kevin: some more plastic products along with her.
Kevin: But he is interested in a hydroponics plant and produce some different crops and whatnot and again kind of choice influencing what?
Kevin: What wears he will provide in this store?
Kevin: Anyway, so we have now a whole plethora of small business people in town
Kevin: and
Kevin: And again, you're trying in my path the good path. I'm obviously helping them join the Union
Kevin: we're all doing the sustainable options and.
Kevin: Healthier options and all this good stuff.
Kevin: Um, and roughly around that point, once you have all three business people in that
Kevin: more or less will lock your, um, if you've done all good options that will lock you
Kevin: out of the TAMI path, general TAMI options will lock you out of the union path.
Kevin: Um, and yeah, obviously the mixed ending will get you prevent you from
Kevin: getting either of the other ones.
Kevin: Um, so, uh, with that said, um, there is still.
Kevin: Some, uh, issues as TAMI not being content with all the new competition in town and
Kevin: the new business people, um, in the good ending, at least, excuse me, um, uh,
Kevin: basically starts, uh, uh, harassing the, the, the town a little bit.
Kevin: Um, and through the, and this is through the means of Elmer, another key
Kevin: character to this, uh, whole, uh, story.
Kevin: uh... elmer is
Kevin: called the city representative he is the
Kevin: representative to the
Kevin: the city itself doesn't have a
Kevin: formal government
Kevin: uh... but
Kevin: uh... he serves as a representative to the nearby local
Kevin: county government's not very clear but uh... he's a good representative
Kevin: uh... elmer is a very
Kevin: let's call him
Kevin: uh...
Kevin: unsure man uh...
Kevin: He's very hesitant, very reluctant.
Kevin: And he bends very easily to Tammy's influence and strong personality.
Kevin: Um, uh, and so, um, as, uh, you have some more discussions with the town and
Kevin: around Elmer, um, it starts to come to light that there are some shady dealings
Kevin: going on from the, the city go or local government, uh, angle.
Kevin: Um, and so you have to go around gathering evidence, investigating
Kevin: Tammy and Omer.
Kevin: Uh, and sure enough, um, you find out that, uh, yeah, Tammy has been
Kevin: manipulating Elmer so much to the point that the town report from the ending
Kevin: of the base game was actually completely altered, basically fabricated, um, by
Kevin: Elmer and there was a true original report, um, which did identify Tammy as
Kevin: the cause of the environmental issues.
Kevin: Um, this was interesting because I, one of the things I liked about the base
Kevin: ending, uh, was kind of this inversion of how the big, you know, industrial
Kevin: business woman was not actually the villain.
Kevin: You were just a really kind of awful person, but not, uh, responsible
Kevin: the ecological damage, um, while the small town business people were responsible.
Kevin: Um, but now they kind of pulled the rug under that.
Kevin: Right.
Kevin: little on that aspect of it and the good ending I'm kind of you know weakening
Kevin: the base ending a little bit but I get it I can live with it you know because
Kevin: you're exciting with these business people and yeah they're making the
Kevin: effort to change or what they thought and they still stick with their practice
Kevin: or whatever so you know shout outs to them I guess but it does you know it
Kevin: It would have been nice to still have that kind of mark against them, but.
Kevin: So be it, regardless though, this point, when you're basically at the end game at this point with the revelations of Elmer,
Kevin: Elmer basically, a town meeting is had, and this is when all the evidence is presented,
Kevin: and Elmer basically buckles under the pressure, admits to the wrongdoing, the corruption, the influence from Tammy,
Kevin: And at that point
Kevin: He basically quits his job with one final action of opening up an election for a new city representative
Kevin: And in the good ending
Kevin: Rose to
Kevin: Aunt Teller actually her father was originally also worked for the local government and
Kevin: believe a mayor I don't recall but
Kevin: She decided to follow in her father's footsteps, and you know start supporting the town. It's some
Kevin: What in?
Kevin: Recompense for her early actions in the base game of trying to expand too much and erasing the town's identity in history
Kevin: And it suits her because it tellers a very strong sort of woman as well so very fitting for her
Kevin: and
Kevin: What is in probably what my favorite part from the good ending is the Derek angle?
Kevin: one of the last
Kevin: aspects of the union to have enough members to be
Kevin: formally recognized by the government, they have to get a seventh or eighth. There's one more
Kevin: business person they need, and they reach out to Derek, who is the local bank manager. And again,
Kevin: he is also Tammy's husband, which obviously puts him in a precarious position. But if you go through
Kevin: the requests and convince Derek to join you, he does so in part because his marriage with Tammy
Kevin: has just been suffering. He points to the fact that there are so many people who are suffering.
Kevin: to a history where she was not so callous and heartless, and he misses basically the woman
Kevin: he originally married. And Derek joining the union is kind of the breaking point along with
Kevin: again the whole town meeting with the new government, new representative, and the new
Kevin: report or the original report being found. Tammy has basically...
Kevin: a breakdown, and she just goes on just outrage. And the next morning, she's actually just
Kevin: completely skipped town, abandoning not just Derek, but they had a son who works with you.
Kevin: Oh gosh, is it Chad? I forget. But yeah, Tammy just disappears from town.
Kevin: And so that's kind of how the game ends at that point.
Kevin: Heller formally hands you over the deed.
Kevin: And his head's off to as her new role as a city representative.
Kevin: And now the union is basically running the economics and business in town.
Kevin: Um, one little asterisk, um, was a Chester might be the son's name, my chest, right?
Kevin: I can't remember off the top of my head.
Kevin: Um, but, um, I wonder if this was an oversight, but in the, uh, as I said,
Kevin: tell her son or not tell her, excuse me, Tammy's son works for you.
Kevin: But in.
Kevin: The ending the good ending he blames you for his mother leaving and angrily announces he'll never talk to you again but gameplay wise it just goes back to work right for you which seems like a bit of an oversight that sort of ending would I would think would have locked him out as well which would have made sense.
Kevin: Um, yeah, but that's, yeah, that's how the game ends Tammy has skipped town.
Kevin: There's no big old business union, working to be sustainable and ecologically friendly, and things are looking bright for the town.
Kevin: Um, yeah, so, again, aside from the tester incident.
Kevin: know kind of her true colors actually showing through which or if they were
Kevin: gonna go that route then just go all in like that yeah I think it was well done
Kevin: um I'm trying to think oh there is one other character I should have mentioned
Kevin: he's not as major of a character but his kind of side story does influence the
Kevin: plot a little bit and then is progression locked behind some of his
Kevin: test. And that is the character...
Kevin: Cornelius. He is a journalist in town who has done some reporting against you,
Kevin: Discounty, in the base game, especially when there's unrest from the town as
Kevin: Discounty tries to expand too much. But he is also the grandson of, I forget, one of the town's
Kevin: founders. And he's obsessed with that kind of, sort of, lineage and wants to honor his great
Kevin: Grandfather, great-grandfather, whatever it was.
Kevin: He ends up building the Blomkest Museum basically, showing the history of the town,
Kevin: including his, again, his ancestors' involvement in the town.
Kevin: It's funny because some of the information is known to be questionable, basically,
Kevin: but people love it because it helps give the town a little more identity.
Kevin: But yeah, so that's kind of the good ending I had for this.
Kevin: Um, yeah, and so overall, thumbs up.
Kevin: Gameplay-wise, story-wise, you know, not perfect, but overall, I enjoyed it and easy, easy recommend.
Kevin: Anyways, but that said, again, the other endings, I haven't experienced them myself,
Kevin: but I have looked into them.
Kevin: The neutral ending is, kind of, it feels a little weak.
Kevin: basically not much changes from where
Kevin: the town starts at the people are profit update Tammy maintains her plants the
Kevin: business owners don't form the Union but they do manage to apply a little
Kevin: pressure towards Tammy as I understand it and so on neither side really backing
Kevin: down so I'll my believe maintains his role as representative and there's not
Kevin: much change in the overall direction of the town that doesn't become
Kevin: more sustainable eco-friendly or whatnot but it doesn't become the bad
Kevin: and that's so the bad ending is interesting because they really kind of
Kevin: go all in so again all this based on what I've read and heard but as I
Kevin: understand it in the bad ending you well you go along with Tammy's plans for
Kevin: expansion and advertising for discounting and growing the business
Kevin: that you basically...
Kevin: he uses you as a pawn to weaken the other business people in town and their union.
Kevin: And at one point, you discover...
Kevin: not super clearly, but basically these major plans for expansion and industrializing the whole town.
Kevin: At which point, Tammy basically locks you in the sewers so you don't reveal the information.
Kevin: You do make your way out of the sewers, um, and I wonder...
Kevin: if that gameplay is a little different. You explore a little bit of that in the good ending.
Kevin: Uh, there are some sewers that you go through as you're investigating for the evidence,
Kevin: but I don't know if it's any different. Um, but I digress. Um, in the bad ending,
Kevin: uh, when you do get out of the sewers, um, it is too late and, um, some of the pollution has
Kevin: just become, uh, basically unsustainable bad levels, uh, influencing others, basically.
Kevin: Um, which is kind of wild, um, where they just become, uh, zombies as I've heard it described.
Kevin: Um, uh, Tammy has placed herself as city representative, and, um, I believe Cornelius
Kevin: actually has just straight up disappeared in the bad ending, which is very interesting,
Kevin: I assume because of his journalism, uh, kind of, and the history connection.
Kevin: um and teller just leaves town actually that is kind of an element she does
Kevin: in all endings handing you the deed but the you know context is clearly different in the good
Kevin: ending she leaves to as you know to fulfill her role as a local representative in the town
Kevin: um but in the bad ending she is just uh basically given up and then
Kevin: moves to start anew elsewhere um you know yeah um it's over the top very evil you know very
Kevin: profit commercial heavy, which.
Kevin: feels, how should I put this, a little almost cartoonish,
Kevin: but given, it's interesting how so many of these,
Kevin: not just this ending, but I feel like there's a handful
Kevin: of medias where, you know, our current,
Kevin: at least out here in the U.S.,
Kevin: political and hyper-capitalist nightmare environment
Kevin: kind of makes you soften on these sort of
Kevin: cartoonish endings a little bit.
Kevin: Yeah, no, that that tracks, I guess.
Kevin: Um, in fact, it might be a little too real now.
Kevin: Um, anyways, um, so yeah, that's a kind of a snapshot of the endings on discounty.
Kevin: Um, they are, yeah, like, so overall, I think the story is pretty solid.
Kevin: Um, this game, unlike, you know, unlike stardew or maybe some of these other
Kevin: farming sims
Kevin: a lot more story heavy
Kevin: Then you know, I appreciate it was good enough
Kevin: Or no, no, not just good enough. It was well done. I think it was well done, you know
Kevin: Maybe a weak point here or there but you know, it's not bad by any means. So thumbs up all around
Kevin: The gameplay I've talked about that at length. I do think I will note one thing
Kevin: I should have mentioned earlier dynamics just number of unlocks you can get with the inventory
Kevin: And then the spacing it really makes running the
Kevin: Store at full capacity pretty challenging to be very frank. I'm in a good way. Um, I
Kevin: You know, you know, what's nice is you can kind of temper a little
Kevin: But as I mentioned there's a mechanic where you put up posters and advertisements and increase customers
Kevin: If you don't do that, you get less customers and it's a little easier to manage
Kevin: And so gonna you can sometimes even use that to your advantage. There are
Kevin: Some through post game after the update
Kevin: A few of them are pretty demanding challenges
Kevin: and it's easier with one of them for instance is doing a number of online orders which is
Kevin: totally separate from the you know separate little area from the main store so my doing
Kevin: a whole bunch of online orders while maintaining client happiness inside the main store which
Kevin: Which is pretty challenging AF2.
Kevin: So having that option to kind of
Kevin: a little for yourself using those advertisements and whatnot much much appreciated.
Kevin: Um, but uh, but yeah, uh, sorry I'm just thinking here.
Kevin: I think that's roughly all I got to say for real now.
Kevin: The the final word on discounty here.
Kevin: Um, good game still thumbs up all the way throughout.
Kevin: Easy recommend it's pretty affordable from what I remember.
Kevin: I'm gonna have the exact price right now.
Kevin: But, uh, uh, yeah, shout out to discounting for being good the whole way, pretty much.
Kevin: Um, you know, just, I wish they could have told me which upgrade the mind first.
Kevin: Uh, anyways.
Kevin: Okay.
Kevin: That's, that's all I've got for, uh, everyone today.
Kevin: Uh, thank you for bearing with us for this, uh, unorthodox episode of the harvest season.
Kevin: Um, uh, but, uh, as always, I'm Kevin.
Kevin: I'm a Cooper is on whatever.
Kevin: If you care to find me, I don't have much of interest.
Kevin: Unfortunately, I didn't promise you all get back to heart one day.
Kevin: Maybe.
Kevin: Um, but, uh, you know, what is interesting is this show that you're listening to and
Kevin: you know, it is cause you're listening.
Kevin: And if you want more of it, uh, head on down to, uh, our Patreon for the harvest season.
Kevin: Uh, I don't have the link.
Kevin: Unfortunately, uh, I'm recording set up.
Kevin: I'm having some internet issues.
Kevin: Um, you know what?
Kevin: Hold on one second.
Kevin: Let's see.
Kevin: Let's see this, all right.
Kevin: I was trying to get the link, but anyways, I digress.
Kevin: Um, sorry about that.
Kevin: Um, anyway, so I was thinking, um, sorry about that.
Kevin: I get distracted.
Kevin: Okay.
Kevin: Um, anyways, you can, uh, check out the, uh, you can check out the website.
Kevin: Uh, at, uh, or harvest season dot club.
Kevin: I hope that was right.
Kevin: Um, to see our show, um, show notes, links, all that good stuff.
Kevin: All the episodes are there.
Kevin: Leave messages, leave feedback.
Kevin: Um, I'm going to address it right now because I'll leave that for future episode.
Kevin: But, uh, uh, look forward to the head comments for Kevin.
Kevin: Um, again, that is, uh, harvest season dot club.
Kevin: I hope that was right.
Kevin: Apologies if I forgot, you'd think I would know it off the top of my head.
Kevin: Um, or you can go to patreon.com/thspot for, um, the, uh, the good stuff, uh, uh,
Kevin: which is all the goodies.
Kevin: It's just for a few bucks a month you can join our patreon
Kevin: access to the slack where people talk about these after these games these
Kevin: episodes all that good stuff. You can also get access to the greenhouse
Kevin: episodes on non farming game themes which are many already and more I have
Kevin: planned you know one day. Aislinn and I are going to do one on worlds the
Kevin: the full experience on Pokemon Worlds.
Kevin: Look forward to that!
Kevin: Just when she's not so busy.
Kevin: She's busy woman with all her airplane piloting stuff.
Kevin: But you know, I'll probably do one on the Nintendo Direct soon too.
Kevin: Not I do that solo.
Kevin: Maybe I don't know how many how much other people care.
Kevin: We'll see.
Kevin: But but yeah.
Kevin: So yeah, follow the Heart of the Season on Patreon on Blue Sky on wherever it's THS pod,
Kevin: the harvest season, look for all those good words.
Kevin: Thank you, Chelsea and Codey, for all the stuff you guys did, the news, and I was
Kevin: starting the episode strong. Thank you, Al, for editing all this nonsense somehow.
Kevin: And thank you, listener, for enduring all this. We made it somehow.
Kevin: Yeah, that'll do it. Oh, I'm just kidding. How could I forget? Should I pick a voice?
Kevin: I don't. Here I am. Let's do it as Toad from the Mario series.
Kevin: [gibberish]
Kevin: Something like that.
Kevin: Boy, that peaked the mic.
Kevin: Hope that caught, uh, but yeah.
Kevin: Take care, everyone. Have a good harvest.
Theme Tune: The Harvest Season is created by Al McKinley with support from our patrons including our
Theme Tune: pro farmers Kevin, Stuart and Elisa. Our art is done by Micah the Brave and our music is
Theme Tune: done by Nick Burgess. Feel free to visit our website harvestseason.club for show notes
Theme Tune: and links to things we discussed in this episode.
Codey: You know, even though I'll like, there's this pre record checklist and it's the same thing
Codey: every single time. But then on days like today, where my brain is potato, I'm like, thankful,
Codey: like, sometimes I'm like, Okay, we, we do the same thing every time. So like,
Codey: why do we need this pre record checklist, right? And then days like today, my brain is like,
Chelsea: Yes.
Codey: No, you need it. I need I need it. Oh, today's world series.
Chelsea: You need it.
Chelsea: No.
Chelsea: Oh no, why is my computer messing up?
Chelsea: No!
Chelsea: No, there we go.
Chelsea: Hello?
Chelsea: Yes?
Codey: I can hear you.
Chelsea: No?
Codey: You went nowhere.
Chelsea: Okay.
Chelsea: Sorry.
Codey: We're fine.
Chelsea: Okay.
Codey: We will survive this time of great hardship.
Chelsea: I think we're both not firing all cylinders today.
Codey: No, I'll comment on it and people can,
Codey: I don't think people will comment on it, they're nice.